Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
[Reborn from the Ashes]
[ولدت من الرماد]
[Episode 4]
[الحلقة 4]
Welcome the eldest daughter back home.
مرحباً بإبنتنا الكبرى في المنزل.
Doesn't the Su Family already have an eldest daughter?
أليس لدى عائلة سو ابنة أكبر بالفعل؟
Then who is this newcomer?
إذن من هو هذا الوافد الجديد؟
Maybe she's a fraud.
ربما أنها محتالة.
She must be after the Su Family's wealth and honor.
لا بد أنها تسعى وراء ثروة وشرف عائلة سو .
My father raised me in the countryside since I was young.
لقد رباني والدي في الريف منذ أن كنت صغيرا.
He feels deeply remorseful about it.
إنه يشعر بالندم الشديد حيال ذلك.
This good luck is for everyone to share.
هذا الحظ السعيد للجميع للمشاركة.
One petal
بتلة واحدة
for one coin.
لعملة واحدة.
Collect as many as you can
اجمع أكبر عدد ممكن
and then bring them
ثم أحضرهم
to my mansion to exchange with my father.
إلى قصري للتبادل مع والدي.
Come and share some good luck.
تعال وشاركنا ببعض الحظ السعيد.
One petal for one coin!
بتلة واحدة مقابل عملة واحدة!
Collect silver coins from Master Su.
اجمع العملات الفضية من المعلم سو.
The show
العرض
is about to begin.
على وشك أن تبدأ.
Master!
يتقن!
Why are you in such a hurry?
لماذا أنت في عجلة من أمرك؟
There's someone outside
هناك شخص بالخارج
claiming to be the legitimate daughter of Su Family.
تدعي أنها الابنة الشرعية لعائلة سو.
The legitimate daughter?
الإبنة الشرعية؟
Master,
يتقن،
looks like Qingran has come back.
يبدو أن تشينغران قد عاد.
Then come back.
ثم عد.
What's the big deal about it?
ما هو الأمر الكبير في هذا الأمر؟
But she brought a crowd of people with her
لكنها أحضرت معها حشدًا من الناس
to ask you for auspicious gifts.
لأطلب منك الهدايا الميمونة.
Each one holds a flower petal in hand.
كل واحد منهم يحمل بتلة زهرة في يده.
They say one petal
يقولون بتلة واحدة
can be exchanged for one coin.
يمكن استبدالها بعملة واحدة.
What?
ماذا؟
They want silver coins?
هل يريدون عملات فضية؟
A crowd of people?
حشد من الناس؟
The lady and those people have been strolling the streets all day.
لقد كانت السيدة وأولئك الأشخاص يتجولون في الشوارع طوال اليوم.
They strolled back and forth four or five times.
لقد تجولوا ذهابا وإيابا أربع أو خمس مرات.
Now, everyone in the city knows
الآن أصبح الجميع في المدينة يعرفون
[Su Mansion] that the eldest daughter
[قصر سو] أن الابنة الكبرى
we abandoned in the countryside
لقد هجرنا في الريف
has returned.
لقد عاد.
I will go outside and welcome the lady back.
سأخرج وأرحب بالسيدة مرة أخرى.
At the same time,
وفي نفس الوقت،
I will teach her the proper manners.
سأعلمها الآداب الصحيحة.
Is this the former home of Zhijin?
هل هذا هو المنزل السابق لـ Zhijin؟
My Lady, you refused to get off the carriage,
سيدتي، لقد رفضت النزول من العربة،
making such a big scene.
صنع مثل هذا المشهد الكبير.
Are you trying to let the whole city
هل تحاول السماح للمدينة بأكملها
laugh at the Su Family?
تضحك على عائلة سو؟
Who are you?
من أنت؟
I am send
انا ارسل
by the Madam to invite you inside.
من قبل السيدة لدعوتك إلى الداخل.
You...
أنت...
Madam?
سيدتي؟
I did not even know
لم أكن أعلم حتى
that my father had remarried after my mother passed away.
أن والدي تزوج مرة أخرى بعد وفاة والدتي.
Or did you deliberately damage the reputation of Su Mansion
أم أنك أضرت عمدا بسمعة قصر سو؟
in front of others?
أمام الآخرين؟
You...
أنت...
You've clearly been living rough in the countryside.
من الواضح أنك كنت تعيش حياة قاسية في الريف.
As the lady of Su Mansion,
بصفتي سيدة قصر سو،
you're behaving so uncouthly.
أنت تتصرف بطريقة غير لائقة.
If you have the guts, get off.
إذا كان لديك الشجاعة، انزل.
I'll teach you some proper manners.
سأعلمك بعض الأخلاق الصحيحة.
Just wait and see.
فقط انتظر وشاهد.
You're just a servant, yet you dare defy me?
أنت مجرد خادم، ومع ذلك تجرؤ على تحديني؟
You hit me again?
ضربتني مرة أخرى؟
I won't just hit you;
لن أضربك فقط؛
I'll have to kick you too.
سوف اضطر إلى ركلك أيضًا.
You...
أنت...
I represent Concubine Gong.
أنا أمثل المحظية غونغ.
Stop barking like a dog here.
توقف عن النباح مثل الكلب هنا.
Bring your master to me at once.
أحضر سيدك إليّ على الفور.
Qingran, no need to be so aggressive.
تشينجران، ليس هناك حاجة إلى أن تكون عدوانيًا جدًا.
You just got back,
لقد عدت للتو
and you've already hurt my servant.
وقد أذيت بالفعل خادمي.
How impressive.
كم هو مثير للإعجاب.
So this is the Concubine Gong whom Zhijin mentioned.
إذن هذه هي المحظية غونغ التي ذكرها تشيجين.
Pay my greetings to you,
أرسل لك تحياتي
Father,
أب،
Grandmother.
جدة.
Why not return to the mansion?
لماذا لا نعود إلى القصر؟
What are you making a fuss about here?
ما الذي يثير ضجة هنا؟
Master, you must stand up for me.
سيدي، يجب عليك أن تدافع عني.
I went out to greet the lady.
خرجت لتحية السيدة.
I never expected to be beaten like this by her.
لم أتوقع أبدًا أن أتعرض للضرب منها بهذه الطريقة.
I have served the Su Family
لقد خدمت عائلة سو
diligently for decades.
بجد واجتهاد لعقود من الزمن.
The lady's doing is truly heartbreaking.
إن ما فعلته السيدة أمر مفجع حقًا.
Qingran, if you have any grievance with me, just say it.
تشينجران، إذا كان لديك أي شكوى معي، فقط قل ذلك.
Right in front of all these people,
أمام كل هؤلاء الناس مباشرة،
you humiliated a servant.
لقد أذللت خادما.
This truly brings shame to the Su Mansion.
وهذا حقا يجلب العار إلى قصر سو.
Your servant,
خادمك
at the gate of Su Mansion,
عند بوابة قصر سو،
slandered the legitimate daughter of the Su Family.
تشويه سمعة الابنة الشرعية لعائلة سو.
That is not bad enough.
هذا ليس سيئا بما فيه الكفاية.
Yet she threw Su Mansion's honor aside
ومع ذلك ألقت شرف قصر سو جانبًا
and spouted nonsense right at the gate.
وأطلق الهراء مباشرة عند البوابة.
As the legitimate daughter, how could I just stand by and watch?
وباعتباري الابنة الشرعية، كيف يمكنني أن أقف مكتوفة الأيدي وأشاهد؟
That wretched servant just now
هذا الخادم البائس الآن
actually dared to call you "Madam".
في الواقع تجرأ على مناداتك بـ "سيدتي".
Though I grew up in the countryside,
على الرغم من أنني نشأت في الريف،
I still understand this much:
لا أزال أفهم هذا القدر:
a wife is a wife,
الزوجة هي الزوجة
and a concubine is a concubine.
والسرية هي سرية.
They can never be the same.
لا يمكن أن يكونوا نفس الشيء أبدًا.
You...
أنت...
What?
ماذا؟
Concubine Gong,
محظية غونغ،
did I say something wrong?
هل قلت شيئا خاطئا؟
The little brat intimidated me as soon as she got back.
لقد أخافتني تلك الطفلة الصغيرة بمجرد عودتها.
If it weren't for making you marry in place of Feiyi,
إذا لم يكن الأمر يتعلق بتزويجك بدلاً من فييي،
you would have died in the brothel.
كنت قد مت في بيت الدعارة.
I will keep today's matter in mind
سأضع مسألة اليوم في الاعتبار
and settle this with you another day.
وسأحل هذا الأمر معك في يوم آخر.
Madam, Master,
سيدتي، سيدي،
today's incident is my fault.
الحادثة اليوم هي خطئي.
I failed to manage my servant properly.
لقد فشلت في إدارة خادمي بشكل صحيح.
It's all because of this lowly servant ruining my reputation
كل هذا بسبب هذا الخادم المتواضع الذي يدمر سمعتي
and stirring trouble between Qingran and me.
وإثارة المشاكل بيني وبين تشينجران.
Someone!
شخص ما!
Give Wang Cuihua 30 lashes with the cane.
اضرب وانغ كوي هوا 30 جلدة بالعصا.
Then send her to a village in the countryside.
ثم أرسلها إلى قرية في الريف.
Concubine Gong, please have mercy!
محظية غونغ، من فضلك ارحمينا!
For my loyalty over these ten years,
لولائي طيلة هذه السنوات العشر،
please spare me this once.
أرجوك أن تجنيني هذا مرة واحدة.
Concubine Gong.
محظية غونغ.
No, please!
لا من فضلك!
Let me go.
دعني أذهب.
I'll leave on my own.
سأغادر بمفردي.
Qingran,
كينغران،
now that you've returned.
الآن بعد أن عدت.
Concubine Gong has found a good match for you.
لقد وجدت المحظية غونغ تطابقًا جيدًا لك.
The marriage alliance with the Prince Zhenbei's Mansion
تحالف الزواج مع قصر الأمير زينبي
is something that countless prestigious families
هو شيء لا حصر له بالنسبة للعائلات المرموقة
in Yunzhou City dream of.
في حلم مدينة يونزو.
Such a perfect match.
إنها مباراة مثالية.
Why not give it to my sister?
لماذا لا أعطيها لأختي؟
You are the eldest daughter.
أنت الابنة الكبرى.
A younger sister can't marry
الاخت الصغرى لا تستطيع الزواج
before her old sister.
أمام أختها الكبرى.
I heard my sister has returned.
سمعت أن أختي عادت.
Su Feiyi? She's actually Zhijin's sister?
سو فيي؟ هل هي في الواقع أخت Zhijin؟
You...
أنت...
You're not Su Qingran.
أنت لست سو تشينغران.
You're that vile woman.
أنت تلك المرأة الشريرة.
Are you crazy?
هل انت مجنون؟
She's crazy.
إنها مجنونة.
As a daughter of a concubine,
كابنة محظية،
she dares to insult me.
إنها تجرؤ على إهانتي.
Bad example from the top leads to ruin below.
المثال السيئ من الأعلى يؤدي إلى الخراب في الأسفل.
Wen Yueqian had her eyes gouged out,
تم اقتلاع عيون وين يويتشيان،
then was thrown off a bottomless cliff.
ثم تم إلقاؤه من على جرف لا نهاية له.
There's no way she survived.
لا توجد طريقة لبقائها على قيد الحياة.
It's hard to believe
من الصعب تصديق ذلك
there could be two people so alike in this world.
من الممكن أن يكون هناك شخصين متشابهين جدًا في هذا العالم.
Feiyi, who do you think I am?
فييي، من تعتقد أنني؟
You seem quite afraid of my appearance.
يبدو أنك خائف جدًا من مظهري.
Everyone is staring at you.
الجميع ينظرون إليك.
Let's talk about this back at the mansion.
دعونا نتحدث عن هذا الأمر في القصر.
Don't embarrass yourself here.
لا تضع نفسك في موقف محرج هنا.
In front of all the city's residents,
أمام جميع سكان المدينة،
that mother and daughter dare treat me this way.
أن الأم وابنتها تجرؤان على معاملتي بهذه الطريقة.
If we return to the mansion and close the doors,
إذا عدنا إلى القصر وأغلقنا الأبواب،
who knows what they might do to me?
من يعلم ماذا قد يفعلون بي؟
What do you all think?
ماذا تعتقدون جميعا؟
Isn't that right?
أليس هذا صحيحا؟
Yes, yes, that's exactly it.
نعم، نعم، هذا هو بالضبط.
Father,
أب،
if outsiders find out,
إذا اكتشف الغرباء ذلك،
they'll say
سيقولون
you can't tell your wife from your concubine,
لا يمكنك التمييز بين زوجتك وجاريتك،
favoring the concubine over the wife.
تفضيل الجارية على الزوجة.
Feiyi, apologize to your sister.
فيي، اعتذر لأختك.
Show her some respect first.
أظهر لها بعض الاحترام أولاً.
After she marries that sickly one who won't live long,
بعد أن تتزوج ذلك المريض الذي لن يعيش طويلاً،
she will suffer a lot.
ستعاني كثيرًا.
So that's how it is.
هكذا هو الأمر.
I was wondering why Su Feiyi didn't marry Wanyan Qi
كنت أتساءل لماذا لم تتزوج Su Feiyi من Wanyan Qi
and they brought Zhijin back home.
وأعادوا تشيجين إلى المنزل.
It turns out
اتضح
that Wanyan Qi's illness has relapsed and he won't last long.
أن مرض وانيان تشي قد انتكست ولن يستمر طويلاً.
Qingran,
كينغران،
I was wrong.
لقد كنت مخطئا.
Please forgive me.
رجائاً أعطني.
Since you admit your mistake,
بما أنك اعترفت بخطئك،
I won't hold it against you.
لن أحملك أي مسؤولية.
From today on,
من اليوم فصاعدا،
I am the only legitimate daughter
أنا الابنة الشرعية الوحيدة
of the Su Family,
من عائلة سو،
Su Qingran.
سو تشينغران.
Good.
جيد.
This is quite interesting indeed.
وهذا مثير للاهتمام حقا.
My Lord,
سيدي
she was the courtesan in the brothel yesterday,
لقد كانت العاهرة في بيت الدعارة أمس،
and she has become Su Family's daughter today.
وأصبحت اليوم ابنة عائلة سو.
She's really extraordinary.
إنها غير عادية حقا.
I have returned to the mansion.
لقد عدت إلى القصر.
Step aside at once.
تنحى جانبا على الفور.
Master Su, please don't leave.
سيد سو، من فضلك لا تغادر.
You still owe us silver coins.
مازلت مدينًا لنا بالعملات الفضية.
One petal for one coin.
بتلة واحدة مقابل عملة واحدة.
Zhijin, these are your family.
تشيجين، هؤلاء هم عائلتك.
In their eyes, you're only a replacement.
في نظرهم، أنت مجرد بديل.
They know the path ahead is a pit of fire,
إنهم يعلمون أن الطريق أمامهم هو حفرة من النار،
but they won't hesitate to push you in.
لكنهم لن يترددوا في دفعك إلى الداخل.
Stop.
قف.
This ends now.
هذا ينتهي الآن.
This is an order from Concubine Gong.
هذا أمر من المحظية غونغ.
Concubine Gong has really tamed you to forget your place.
لقد قامت المحظية غونغ بترويضك حقًا لتنسى مكانك.
I am the legitimate daughter
أنا الابنة الشرعية
of the Su Family.
من عائلة سو.
Even if Concubine Gong stands here,
حتى لو كانت المحظية غونغ تقف هنا،
I am still the one to be respected.
أنا لا أزال الشخص الذي يجب احترامه.
Now leave at once.
الآن أغادر على الفور.
It must feel awful to follow the wrong master.
لا بد وأن يكون من السيء للغاية أن تتبع المعلم الخطأ.
You gave your all for someone
لقد أعطيت كل ما لديك لشخص ما
who then discarded you like an old shoe.
الذي تخلى عنك بعد ذلك مثل الحذاء القديم.
Right now, there's an opportunity.
الآن، هناك فرصة.
It's up to you whether to take it.
يعتمد الأمر عليك فيما إذا كنت تريد أن تأخذه أم لا.
Work for me.
اعمل معي.
What a spendthrift!
يا له من تبذير!
She has cost me dearly.
لقد كلفتني غاليا.
Father.
أب.
Father,
أب،
she suffered such grave injuries.
لقد عانت من إصابات خطيرة.
It's best not to punish her.
من الأفضل عدم معاقبتها.
Why not let her follow me from now on?
لماذا لا أدعها تتبعني من الآن فصاعدا؟
If you like,
إذا أردت،
she can follow you.
يمكنها أن تتبعك.
Father.
أب.
What is it now?
ما هو الآن؟
I still don't know
انا لا اعرف بعد
where I will stay.
حيث سأبقى.
Stay at Qinyuan Garden for now.
اقم في حديقة تشين يوان في الوقت الحالي.
Oh no, I've never been here before.
أوه لا، لم أكن هنا من قبل.
Where exactly is Qinyuan Garden?
أين تقع حديقة تشين يوان بالضبط؟
Get up quickly and go back to Qinyuan Garden with me.
استيقظ بسرعة و عد إلى حديقة تشين يوان معي.
Hmph.
همف.
Get up quickly.
انهض بسرعة.
Qinyuan Garden is this way.
حديقة تشين يوان تقع في هذا الطريق.
I'll go back with you.
سأعود معك.
My Lady,
سيدتي،
this is some fresh cherries I just picked.
هذه بعض الكرز الطازج الذي قطفته للتو.
Try some while they're fresh.
جرب بعضها بينما لا تزال طازجة.
If you need anything else, just let me know.
إذا كنت بحاجة إلى أي شيء آخر، فقط أخبرني.
Thank you for your kindness, Cuihua.
شكرا لك على لطفك، كويوا.
I don't like eating cherries.
أنا لا أحب أكل الكرز.
My Lady,
سيدتي،
I remember you love cherries the most.
أتذكر أنك تحب الكرز أكثر من أي شيء آخر.
Eating cherries will make me break out in red rashes
أكل الكرز يسبب لي طفح جلدي أحمر
and not catch my breath.
ولم أستطع التقاط أنفاسي.
I didn't expect Zhijin to like cherries so much.
لم أتوقع أن تشيجين يحب الكرز كثيرًا.
Looks like I have to be more careful in the future,
يبدو أنني سأضطر إلى أن أكون أكثر حذرًا في المستقبل،
to avoid raising any suspicions.
لتجنب إثارة أية شكوك.
Maybe it's because
ربما يكون ذلك بسبب
I ate too many wild cherries in the countryside.
لقد أكلت الكثير من الكرز البري في الريف.
Once, my tooth got sensitive from the sourness.
في إحدى المرات، أصبحت أسناني حساسة بسبب الحموضة.
After that,
بعد ذلك،
I rarely ate them.
نادرا ما أكلتهم.
Put it here for now.
ضعها هنا الآن.
I'll eat it later.
سوف آكله لاحقا.
It is my fault for being careless.
إنه خطئي لأنني مهمل.
These past few days,
في الأيام القليلة الماضية،
thanks for your hard work.
شكرا على عملك الجاد.
Go and rest first.
اذهب واسترح أولاً.
I'm more than happy
أنا أكثر من سعيد
to serve you.
لخدمتك.
I'm not tired at all.
أنا لست متعبة على الإطلاق.
Oh, right, My Lady,
أوه، صحيح، سيدتي،
in a few days will be Lady Feiyi's birthday.
في غضون أيام قليلة سيكون عيد ميلاد السيدة فيي.
Master and
سيد و
Concubine Gong
غونغ المحظية
will host a birthday celebration for Lady Feiyi.
سوف يستضيف احتفالًا بعيد ميلاد السيدة فييي.
I've also prepared
لقد قمت بإعدادها أيضًا
several new outfits for you.
عدة ملابس جديدة لك.
How about
ماذا عن
I bring them over and have you try them on?
أحضرهم إليك وأطلب منك تجربتهم؟
Go ahead.
تفضل.
Bring them over so you can try them.
أحضرهم حتى تتمكن من تجربتهم.
My Lady, please rest assured.
سيدتي، من فضلك اطمئني.
If Lady Feiyi and Concubine Gong dare to bully you,
إذا تجرأت السيدة فييي والمحظية غونغ على إزعاجك،
I'll be the first to oppose them.
سأكون أول من يعارضهم.
I,
أنا،
Wang Cuihua,
وانغ كويهوا,
swear to protect you to the death.
أقسم على حمايتك حتى الموت.
Go now.
اذهب الآن.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Birth
الولادة
day
يوم
celebration.
احتفال.
♪In this world, who exactly♪
???في هذا العالم من بالضبط؟؟؟
♪Pushed me into the abyss?♪
???دفعني إلى الهاوية ؟؟؟؟
♪The sky is silent, and the sea says nothing♪
"السماء صامتة والبحر لا يقول شيئا"
♪Who shows me mercy in this world?♪
???من يرحمني في الدنيا؟؟؟؟
♪Cold winds sweep across the wasteland♪
???رياح باردة تكتسح الأرض القاحلة؟؟؟
♪Mercilessly gifting me snow and frost♪
???يمنحني الثلج والصقيع بلا رحمة؟؟؟
♪In this fleeting life♪
''في هذه الحياة العابرة''
♪No mercy, no answers♪
???لا رحمة، لا إجابات؟؟؟
♪Yet one lamp shines, unafraid to go out♪
ومع ذلك فإن مصباحًا واحدًا يضيء، ولا يخاف من الانطفاء؟؟؟
♪Time can twist, but people aren't perfect♪
???قد يتغير الزمن، لكن الناس ليسوا كاملين؟؟؟
♪Who decides who comes and who parts?♪
???من يقرر من يأتي ومن يفارق ؟؟؟؟
♪It all rests on a single hopeful thought♪
"كل هذا يعتمد على فكرة واحدة مفعمة بالأمل"
♪Why fear one last breath?♪
لماذا الخوف من النفس الأخير؟
♪Love is brief, full of regrets♪
???الحب قصير، مليء بالندم؟؟؟
♪I paint the sky as a fan♪
???أرسم السماء كمروحة؟؟؟
♪To blow away nightmares and scatter the dust♪
???لإزالة الكوابيس وتبديد الغبار؟؟؟
♪Can't resist the fate of being separated♪
???لا تستطيع مقاومة مصير الانفصال؟؟؟
♪By distance♪
???بالمسافة؟؟؟
[Exclusive content rights reserved]
[حقوق المحتوى الحصري محفوظة]
[by Youku Information Technology (Beijing) Co., Ltd.]
[من قبل شركة يوكو لتكنولوجيا المعلومات (بكين) المحدودة]